Bavin Edwards

SENIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Details

Kingston

Jamaica

18768590531

bavin_edwards@live.com

Links

LinkedIn

Portfolio

Skills

Node.js

HTML5

CSS

Redux

Git

Typescript

React

JavaScript

Vue

Profile

Passionate and experience web developer with proven industry experience working in agile teams to deliver beautiful, responsive and user-friendly web applications. Experienced with creating component-based user interfaces, unit and integration testing, debugging, state management, authentication and code quality management.

Employment History

Senior Web Developer, Alessa, Kingston, Jamaica

AUGUST 2022 - PRESENT

- Hands-on research and development of the architecture and features for data analytic, and consumer-facing web platforms, which serves major financial institutions worldwide.
- Attend weekly architecture meetings to decide on implementation of future features.
- Facilitate weekly code review sessions to promote growth, great code quality, and a solid understanding of the goals of the project.
- Review pull requests from other developers to ensure code quality, testing and robustness.

Web Developer, Alessa, Kingston, Jamaica

OCTOBER 2021 - AUGUST 2022

Hands-on research and development of the architecture and features for data analytic, and consumer-facing web platforms, which serves major financial institutions worldwide.

Software Developer, Smart Mobile Solutions, Kingston, Jamaica

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2021

- Developing Business Web and Mobile Applications using modern technologies and adhering to industry best practices.
- Created on-boarding Java SpringBoot course and accompanying assessment for new hires.

Education

BSc General Physics, University of the West Indies, Mona, Kingston, Jamaica

AUGUST 2013 - FEBRUARY 2017

- · Engineering scholarship, sophomore year
- Graduated with honors